

# EDUARDO BLANCO RIVAS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER // HTLM5 // Javascript // CSS3 // Node.js // React // DOM // Vite // Git

# DETAILS

MADRID, España eduardoblanco1987@gmail.com 602488895

### PROFILE

I am a Full Stack developer, I trained in the area of law and gastronomic management but since 2020 I decided to embark on a change of life towards programming, going through basic knowledge of IT and basic Python, but fully entering the area of WEB DEVELOPER.

I am a faithful believer that teamwork is a fundamental pillar of any company to achieve maximum efficiency, which is why my coworkers consider me a worker who is involved not only with the company but also with the staff.

It makes good use of JavaScript methods and logic such as manipulating the HTML Dom, as well as making use of libraries such as Tailwind and Bootstarp to create unique applications using CSS. Also, I have the ability to work with control systems mainly Git.

Although I have finished my training relatively recently, I feel empowered to be able to apply what I have learned in your company and also to be able to learn from everything that is always needed in this world of development and is always changing.

My goal is to apply everything obtained so far to achieve the best possible results in your company. Currently I have just finished studying full stack development giving me the initial knowledge to undertake in a new area.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Purchase and logistic Manager, Kilómetros de Pizza SLU, Madrid , MADRID

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

- 1. Managing budget control.
- 2. Prepare budgets depending on the expected sale.
- 3. Manage and supervise personnel and correct distribution of tasks.
- 4. Adjust purchases to 24% of raw material.

#### Unit Manager, Compass Group, MADRID

JUNE 2019 - MARCH 2020

- 1. Manage budget control.
- 2. Prepare budgets depending on the expected sale.
- 3. Supervision of personnel and correct distribution of tasks.
- 4. Preparation of the offer to be presented to the client.

# EDUCATION

# Full Stack Development, Neoland, Madrid

SEPTEMBER 2022 - JANUARY 2023

# Data science, Code-Academy, MADRID

JULY 2021 - JULY 2021

# Advances Styling with responsive Design, Michigan State University (Coursera), MADRID

NOVEMBER 2020 - JANUARY 2020

# Crash Course , Google (Coursera), Madrid

NOVEMBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021

LINKS	
<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Github</u> <u>Personal Portfolio</u>	
SKILLS	
CSS3	Angular
React	HTML5
MongoDB	Git
Java	JavaScript
Solución creativa de problemas	Node.js
LANGUAGES	
Ingles	Español; Castellano